Guide to the James Ferlo Papers, 1963-2015 AIS.1998.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Pennsylvania State Senate, 2000-2015; 2004-2013; II.
  - State Finances, 2001-2015; 2005-2011; 5.
    - Funding Correspondence, 2001-2015
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, September 2008 (Box 86, Folder 13)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, May 2009 (Box 86, Folder 14)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, March 2010 (Box 86, Folder 15)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, August 2010 (Box 86, Folder 16)
      - Department of Conservation and Natural Resources, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 17)
      - DePaul Institute, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 18)
      - Disproportionate Share, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 19)
      - Dollar Energy, 2004-2006 (Box 86, Folder 20)
      - Domestic Violence, 2008-2009 (Box 86, Folder 21)
      - Drug and Alcohol Funding, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 22)
      - Drugs and Alcohol, 2003-2007 (Box 86, Folder 23)
      - Early Childhood Education, 2008-2010 (Box 86, Folder 24)
      - East Liberty, 2010-2011 (Box 86, Folder 25)
      - East Liberty Concerned Citizens Corporation (ELCCC), 2011 (Box 86, Folder 26)
      - East Liberty Concerned Citizens, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 27)
      - East Liberty Development Initiative, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 28)
      - East Northside Action Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 86, Folder 29)
      - Eastside Development, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 30)
      - Economic Stimulus, 2009 (Box 86, Folder 31)
      - Energy and Environmental Community Outreach Center, 2010-2012 (Box 86, Folder 32)
      - Energy Innovation Center (EIC), 2012-2013 (Box 86, Folder 33)
      - Enterprise Zone Program, 2006 (Box 86, Folder 34)
      - Envirothon, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 35)
      - Epilepsy, 2005-2006 (Box 86, Folder 36)
      - Family Support Centers, 2007 (Box 86, Folder 37)
      - Food Programs, 2005-2009 (Box 86, Folder 38)
      - Foundations (Pittsburgh Foundation, Heinz Endowments), 2009-2010 (Box 86, Folder 39)
      - Fox Chapel Area School District, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 40)
      - Freeport-Leechburg-Apollo Group Inc.-Department of Community and Economic Development Funding Years 4-5, 2007-2013 (Box 86, Folder 41)
      - Freeport Borough, 2003-2005 (Box 86, Folder 42)
      - Gaming and Tourism Fund, 2008-2009 (Box 86, Folder 43)
      - General Requests, 2006 (Box 86, Folder 44)
      - General Services, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 45)
      - Gifted Education, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 46)
      - Gilpin Township Camera, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 47)
      - Glenshaw Glass, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Governor's School, 2009 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Grants, 2009-2010 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Grant Endorsement Responses, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Growing Greener II, 2004-2005 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Hazardous Site Cleanup Fund, 2007 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Heinz History Center, 2007-2008 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Heth's Run Bridge Project, 2001 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - Higher Education, 2003-2006 (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - Historic Preservation Grants/Tax Credits, 2012 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - Housing Authority Budget, 2007-2008 (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - Human Services, 2003-2007 (Box 87, Folder 12)
      - Hyde Park Borough, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 13)
      - Independent Living, 2008 (Box 87, Folder 14)
      - Industrial Site Reuse Program, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - Institutional Access Grants, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 16)
      - Junior Achievement, 2007 (Box 87, Folder 17)
      - Kingsley Association, 2009-2011 (Box 87, Folder 18)
      - Larimer Consensus Group, 2011 (Box 87, Folder 19)
      - Lawrenceville Sidewalk Project, 2009 (Box 87, Folder 20)
      - Lawrenceville Youth Football, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 21)
      - Leechburg Borough, 2003-2006 (Box 87, Folder 22)
      - Libraries for the Blind, 2007 (Box 87, Folder 23)
      - Libraries, 2003-2004 (Box 87, Folder 24)
      - Lincoln Larimer Kingsley Community Center Project, 2006 (Box 87, Folder 25)
      - Local Development Districts, 2006-2007 (Box 87, Folder 26)
      - Manchester Craftsmen Guild, 2003-2010 (Box 87, Folder 27)
      - Math Counts, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 28)
      - Mattress Factory, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 29)
      - Medicaid, 2004-2010 (Box 87, Folder 30)
      - Medical Assistance, 2003-2010 (Box 87, Folder 31)
      - Mental Health/Mental Retardation, 2004-2006 (Box 87, Folder 32)
      - Millvale Curve/Park, 2012 (Box 87, Folder 33)
      - Millvale Riverfront Park, 2011-2012 (Box 87, Folder 34)
      - Millvale, 2006 (Box 87, Folder 35)
      - Natrona, 2012 (Box 87, Folder 36)
      - Non-Preferred Appropriations, 2006-2007 (Box 87, Folder 37)
      - Northside Leadership, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 38)
      - PA Council on the Arts, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 39)
      - PA Higher Education Assistance Agency (PHEAA), 2003-2008 (Box 87, Folder 40)
      - PA Historical and Museum Commission, 2005-2009 (Box 87, Folder 41)
      - PA Historical and Museum Commission Meeting, March 16, 2011 (Box 87, Folder 42)
      - PA Historical and Museum Commission Meeting, June 15, 2011 (Box 87, Folder 43)
      - PA Historical and Museum Commission Meeting, June 13, 2012 (Box 87, Folder 44)
      - PA Historical and Museum Commission Meeting, February 6, 2013 (Box 87, Folder 45)
      - PA Historical and Museum Commission Meeting, Sept 24, 2015 (Box 87, Folder 46)
      - PA Starnet, 2011 (Box 87, Folder 47)
      - PA State Troopers Association, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 48)
      - Parks Township, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 49)
      - Pennsylvania Housing Finance Agency, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 50)
      - Pennsylvania Law Enforcement Accreditation, 2007 (Box 87, Folder 51)
      - Pennsylvania Map, 2008 (Box 87, Folder 52)
      - Pennsylvania Schools, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 53)
      - Pennsylvania Water Planning, 2004-2008 (Box 87, Folder 54)
      - Pennsylvania Zoological Council, 2008 (Box 87, Folder 55)
      - PENNVEST, 2005-2006 (Box 87, Folder 56)
      - Personal Care Homes, 2008-2009 (Box 87, Folder 57)
      - PHMC Grants, 2009 (Box 87, Folder 58)
      - Pharmaceutical Assistance Contact for the Elderly (PACE), 2002-2005 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Phipp's Conservatory, 2006 (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - Pittsburgh Community Services, Inc. (PCSI), 2014 (Box 88, Folder 3)
      - Pittsburgh Community Services, Inc. (PCSI), 2014 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Pittsburgh Cultural Trust, 2006-2007 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - Pittsburgh Finance Plans, 2004 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - Pittsburgh Finance Plans, 2004 (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - Pittsburgh Finances Meeting Info, September 8, 2004 (Box 88, Folder 8)
      - Pittsburgh Finances Meeting Info, September 8, 2004 (Box 88, Folder 9)
      - Pittsburgh Finances, 2007-2009 (Box 88, Folder 10)
      - Pittsburgh Life Sciences Greenhouse, 2013 (Box 88, Folder 11)
      - Pittsburgh Opera, 2008 (Box 88, Folder 12)
      - Pittsburgh Super Computing Center, 2005-2009 (Box 88, Folder 13)
      - Pittsburgh Super Computing Center, 2013 (Box 88, Folder 14)
      - Pittsburgh Symphony, 2006-2007 (Box 88, Folder 15)
      - Pittsburgh Women's Center and Shelter, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 16)
      - Planned Parenthood, 2006 (Box 88, Folder 17)
      - Porous Pavement-Environment and Energy Community Outreach Center (EECOC), 2011 (Box 88, Folder 18)
      - Port of Pittsburgh, 2005-2008 (Box 88, Folder 19)
      - Project 15206 Committee Members, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 20)
      - Project 15206 ECO Art PGH, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 21)
      - Project 15206 Foundation Packet, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 22)
      - Project 15206 Funding Opportunities, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 23)
      - Project 15206 Fundraising, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 24)
      - Project 15206 Green Stormwater Infrastructure (GSI) Sites, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 25)
      - Project 15206 Heth's Run Ecological and Recreational Restoration Project, 2008 (Box 88, Folder 26)
      - Project 15206 Meetings, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 27)
      - Project 15206 Meetings, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 28)
      - Project 15206 Misc. Documents, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 29)
      - Project 15206 Public Policy Committee, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 30)
      - Project 15206 Rain Container Sign-Ups, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 31)
      - Project 15206 Site Information, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 32)
      - Project 15206 Site Photographs, ca 2014 (Box 88, Folder 33)
      - Project 15206 Site Selection, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 34)
      - Project 15206 Site Summary Documents, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 35)
      - Project 15206 Stormworks, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 36)
      - Project 15206 Western Pennsylvania Conservancy/Treevitalize, undated (Box 88, Folder 37)
      - Project 15206/Public Policy Committee, 2014 (Box 88, Folder 38)
      - Rape Crisis Centers, 2008 (Box 88, Folder 39)
      - Recycling, 2009 (Box 88, Folder 40)
      - Red Zone, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 41)
      - Redevelopment Assistance Capital Program, 2005-2008 (Box 88, Folder 42)
      - Reserve Township, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 43)
      - Rivers of Steel Heritage Trail, 2007 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - Riverside Center for Innovation, 2003-2005 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - Riverview Park Veteran's Memorial, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - Rockport Airport, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - Route 28 Expansion, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - SB850 Opposition, 2008 (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - Scotland School, 2009 (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - Small Business Development Centers, 2004-2010 (Box 89, Folder 8)
      - Smoking, ca 2003 (Box 89, Folder 9)
      - SSI Supplement, 2009 (Box 89, Folder 10)
      - Stanley Construction Corp., 2006 (Box 89, Folder 11)
      - State Police, 2005-2009 (Box 89, Folder 12)
      - Tech Collaborative, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 13)
      - Thar Process, Inc. Loan, 2012 (Box 89, Folder 14)
      - Three Rivers Art Festival, 2007 (Box 89, Folder 15)
      - Three Rivers Center for Independent Living, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 16)
      - Three Rivers Wet Weather Project, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 17)
      - Three Rivers Wet Weather, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 18)
      - Tucibat, Marlane (Hazard Mitigation Grant Program), 2013-2014 (Box 89, Folder 19)
      - Tuskegee Airmen Memorial, 2012 (Box 89, Folder 20)
      - United Way, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 21)
      - Upper Kiski Valley Medical and Health Authority, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 22)
      - US Steel, 2008 (Box 89, Folder 23)
      - Vandegrift Improvement Program (VIP), 2008-2009 (Box 89, Folder 24)
      - Vandergrift Community Development, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 25)
      - Vandergrift Library, 2007 (Box 89, Folder 26)
      - Vandergrift, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 27)
      - Veterans Outreach and Assistance Center, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 28)
      - Veterans, 2007-2010 (Box 89, Folder 29)
      - WAMs Grants, 2008-2009 (Box 89, Folder 30)
      - WAMs Grants, 2010-2011 (Box 89, Folder 31)
      - Water 1, 2006-2010 (Box 89, Folder 32)
      - Watson Institute, 2008 (Box 89, Folder 33)
      - Weed and Seed, 2011 (Box 89, Folder 34)
      - West Penn Allegheny System, 2005-2013 (Box 89, Folder 35)
      - Western PA School for the Blind, 2003-2005 (Box 89, Folder 36)
      - Westmoreland County, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 37)
      - Westmoreland County Transportation Issues, 2002-2004 (Box 89, Folder 38)
      - Willowbrook Road, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 39)
      - Wineries, 2009 (Box 89, Folder 40)
      - World Trade, PA, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 41)
      - World War II Memorial, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 42)
      - Young Preservationists Association, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 43)
    - Tax Issues
      - 5% Tax (Payroll), 2002 (Box 89, Folder 44)
      - Act 77-Property Tax, 2008-2010 (Box 89, Folder 45)
      - Amusement Taxes, 2008 (Box 89, Folder 46)
      - Brewery Tax Credit, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 47)
      - Budget Loopholes, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 48)
      - Business Tax Changes, 2008 (Box 89, Folder 49)
      - Business Taxes, 2009 (Box 89, Folder 50)
      - Combined Reporting, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 51)
      - County Sales Tax, 2009 (Box 89, Folder 52)
      - County Visitability Tax Credit, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 53)
      - Cracker Plant, 2012 (Box 89, Folder 54)
      - Cracker Plant, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 55)
      - Earned Income Tax Consolidation, 2006-2008 (Box 89, Folder 56)
      - Film Tax Credit, 2008 (Box 89, Folder 57)
      - Film Tax Credit, 2009 (Box 89, Folder 58)
      - Gas Tax, 2003-2008 (Box 89, Folder 59)
      - Historic Tax Credit Coalition, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 60)
      - Kennywood- Amusement Tax, ca 2004 (Box 89, Folder 61)
      - Keystone Innovation Zones, 2012 (Box 89, Folder 62)
      - Local Tax Fairness, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 63)
      - Motorcoach and Mass Transit Oil Tax, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 64)
      - Occupation Tax, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 65)
      - PA Property Tax/Rent Rebate, 2008-2010 (Box 89, Folder 66)
      - Personal Income Tax Reduction, 2007 (Box 89, Folder 67)
      - Personal Income Tax Reduction, 2007 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Property Assessments, 2011-2012 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Property Tax- Rebate, 2009 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Property Tax Reduction, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Property Taxes, 2008 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Realty Transfer, 2005-2007 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Research and Development Tax Credit, 2001-2003 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Residential Tenant Lease Tax, 2007 (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - Sales Tax Vendor's Allowance, 2009 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Sales Tax, 2003-2011 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - Severance Tax, 2009-2011 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - Smokeless Tobacco, 2003-2009 (Box 90, Folder 12)
      - Star Bonds, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 13)
      - State Taxes, 2002-2007 (Box 90, Folder 14-15)
      - Tax Credits, 2009 (Box 90, Folder 16)
      - Tax Credits, 2010-2011 (Box 90, Folder 17)
      - Tax Revenue, 2009 (Box 90, Folder 18)
      - Taxation Manual, 2007-2009 (Box 90, Folder 19)
      - Taxation Manual, 2007-2009 (Box 90, Folder 20)
      - Vehicle Rental Tax, 2002-2003 (Box 90, Folder 21)